Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Vengeful Wife=
=زوجة انتقامية=
=Episode 18=
=الحلقة 18=
Step by step,
خطوة بخطوة،
climbing over countless shoulders,
التسلق على أكتاف لا تعد ولا تحصى،
I finally reached this position.
لقد وصلت أخيرا إلى هذا الموقف.
As the CFO of a major group,
باعتباري المدير المالي لمجموعة كبيرة،
do you know how much I've sacrificed?
هل تعلم كم ضحيت؟
I seem like
انا ابدو مثل
an invincible career woman.
امرأة مهنية لا تقهر.
Truth is, I'm exhausted.
الحقيقة هي أنني مرهق.
I want someone
أريد شخص ما
to lean on.
الاعتماد عليه.
Someone who truly understands me
شخص يفهمني حقًا
and protects me.
ويحميني.
What a pity.
يا للأسف.
Men in this world
الرجال في هذا العالم
rarely meet my standards.
نادرا ما تفي بمعاييري.
Drink up!
اشرب!
Why aren't you drinking?
لماذا لا تشرب؟
Is the wine bad
هل النبيذ سيء؟
or am I not tempting enough?
أم أنني لست مغريا بما فيه الكفاية؟
This wine
هذا النبيذ
is really strong.
إنه قوي حقا.
Then drink more!
ثم اشرب المزيد!
Get going and you won't feel dizzy.
ابدأ ولن تشعر بالدوار.
Here.
هنا.
Cheers.
هتافات.
How exhilarating.
كم هو مبتهج!
Sorry.
آسف.
How clumsy I am.
كم أنا أخرق.
You should take a shower.
ينبغي عليك الاستحمام.
I have pajamas.
لدي بيجامة.
I'll take a shower.
سأستحم.
(Ye Dong) (How is it going?)
(يي دونغ) (كيف حالك؟)
(Qin Yufei) (He went to shower.)
(تشين يوفي) (ذهب للاستحمام.)
(It's about time.)
(لقد حان الوقت.)
Why do I feel dizzy?
لماذا أشعر بالدوار؟
This wine smells good.
هذا النبيذ له رائحة طيبة.
This is not enough to drink.
هذا ليس كافيا للشرب.
Bring the bottle over.
أحضر الزجاجة.
Today, let's drink
اليوم دعونا نشرب
until we're drunk!
حتى نصبح في حالة سُكر!
Fine.
بخير.
Hurry up.
اسرع.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
you'll miss the great part.
سوف تفوتك الجزء العظيم.
Ye Dong,
يي دونغ,
stop having those ill intentions.
توقف عن هذه النوايا السيئة.
I trust Cheng Nuo.
أنا أثق في تشينغ نوو.
Even if you framed him today,
حتى لو قمت بتوريطه اليوم،
I believe
انا أؤمن
he'd never betray me.
لن يخونني أبدًا.
Your underhanded tricks
حيلك الماكرة
only prove your vileness.
فقط أثبت حقدك
How could I frame him?
كيف يمكنني الإيقاع به؟
Your intuition
حدسك
is unreliable sometimes.
غير موثوق بها في بعض الأحيان.
Seeing is believing.
نظرا لصدقه.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Do you think
هل تعتقد
all men are as rotten as you?
هل كل الرجال فاسدون مثلك؟
Today I'll show you
اليوم سأعرض لكم
the difference between you
الفرق بينكما
and him.
وهو.
The gulf between you and him
الفجوة بينك وبينه
can never be bridged.
لا يمكن جسرها أبدًا.
As a demon wallowing in filth,
كشيطان يتخبط في القذارة،
you'll never know human decency.
لن تعرف أبدًا معنى الكرامة الإنسانية.
Fine.
بخير.
We'll see about that.
سوف نرى ذلك.
I wonder when you'll admit the truth.
أتساءل متى سوف تعترف بالحقيقة.
Open the door.
افتح الباب.
Cheng Nuo!
تشينغ نو!
Honey.
عسل.
It's not how it seems.
إنه ليس كما يبدو.
Men
الرجال
are all the same.
كلها متشابهة.
Honey.
عسل.
Are you
أنت
heartbroken now?
هل أنت حزين الآن؟
For someone who doesn't love you,
بالنسبة لشخص لا يحبك،
it's not worth it.
إنه لا يستحق ذلك.
Stop!
قف!
Bai Cha,
باي تشا,
only I'm crazy for you
أنا فقط مجنون بك
and obsessed with you.
ومهووسة بك.
I'll never leave you.
لن أتركك أبدًا.
Even after you married him,
حتى بعد أن تزوجته،
and even when
وحتى عندما
you carried his child,
لقد حملت طفله
I never gave up on you.
لم أتخلى عنك أبدًا.
Lin Xia.
لين شيا.
She is the one
هي هي
countless men covet.
يشتاق إليه عدد لا يحصى من الرجال.
For your sake,
من اجلك
I married into the Lin family,
لقد تزوجت من عائلة لين،
facing ridicule
مواجهة السخرية
and humiliation.
والإذلال.
But I kept thinking I can give you
ولكنني بقيت أفكر أنني أستطيع أن أعطيك
a life of high society by doing so.
حياة المجتمع الراقي من خلال القيام بذلك.
That's what drives me.
هذا ما يدفعني .
For you,
لك،
I've recklessly
لقد فعلت ذلك بتهور
erased every trace of the Lin family.
تم محو كل أثر لعائلة لين.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
I love you so much, right?
أنا أحبك كثيرًا، أليس كذلك؟
You've
لقد
only loved yourself.
احب نفسك فقط.
Ye Dong,
يي دونغ,
listen carefully.
استمع بعناية.
I won't have feelings for anyone,
لن يكون لدي مشاعر تجاه أي شخص،
especially for you.
خاصة بالنسبة لك.
What must I do
ماذا يجب أن أفعل؟
to make you believe
لتجعلك تؤمن
that I love you?
أني أحبك؟
For you,
لك،
I can sacrifice everything.
أستطيع التضحية بكل شيء.
I want your life.
أريد حياتك.
Will you give it?
هل ستعطيها؟
Fine.
بخير.
But I want you
ولكنني أريدك
to die with me.
أن تموت معي.
You really are a madman.
أنت مجنون حقا.
However,
لكن،
I'll give you one chance.
سأعطيك فرصة واحدة.
I want to be the CEO
أريد أن أصبح الرئيس التنفيذي
of Jiuyao Group.
من مجموعة جيوياو.
Do you dare to make a former nightclub hostess
هل تجرؤ على جعل مضيفة ملهى ليلي سابقة
as CEO?
كرئيس تنفيذي؟
If you can't do it,
إذا لم تتمكن من فعل ذلك،
don't come to me again.
لا تأتي إلي مرة أخرى.
♪Like a forgotten flower♪
♪مثل زهرة منسية♪
♪Silently scattered across the horizon♪
♪منتشرة بصمت عبر الأفق♪
♪Bathed in silent starlight♪
♪ مغمورة في ضوء النجوم الصامت♪
♪One day it will bloom♪
♪سوف تزدهر يوما ما♪
♪Let time heal the wounds♪
♪دع الوقت يشفي الجروح♪
♪Clench the trembling hands♪
♪اضغط على يديك المرتعشتين♪
♪Embrace the faith of rebirth♪
♪احتضن إيمان الولادة الجديدة♪
♪The ending won't come too late♪
♪النهاية لن تأتي متأخرة جدًا♪
♪Under the mask♪
♪تحت القناع♪
♪Observing all truths and lies♪
♪مراقبة كل الحقائق والأكاذيب♪
♪Who can see my strength♪
♪من يستطيع رؤية قوتي♪
♪Tears soak my face♪
♪الدموع تغمر وجهي♪
♪Under the mask♪
♪تحت القناع♪
♪Seeking light in the darkness♪
♪البحث عن النور في الظلام♪
♪What couldn't be let go♪
♪ما لا يمكن التخلي عنه♪
♪Eventually turns to dust in the wind♪
♪يتحول في النهاية إلى غبار في الريح♪
♪Under the mask♪
♪تحت القناع♪
♪Observing all truths and lies♪
♪مراقبة كل الحقائق والأكاذيب♪
♪Who can see my strength♪
♪من يستطيع رؤية قوتي♪
♪Tears soak my face♪
♪الدموع تغمر وجهي♪
♪Under the mask♪
♪تحت القناع♪
♪Seeking light in the darkness♪
♪البحث عن النور في الظلام♪
♪What couldn't be let go♪
♪ما لا يمكن التخلي عنه♪
♪Eventually turns to dust in the wind♪
♪يتحول في النهاية إلى غبار في الريح♪